{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947848840109","data":{"timestamp":" 947848840109"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142017"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947848879887","data":{"timestamp":" 947848879887"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142017"," gameId":" 5a7acf86-e22f-4cb7-912a-55b273047a4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_yeduyamo_jigogiki_dovimahu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947848887410","data":{"timestamp":" 947848887410"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142017"," gameId":" 5a7acf86-e22f-4cb7-912a-55b273047a4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_yeduyamo_jigogiki_dovimahu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947848894226","data":{"timestamp":" 947848894226"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142017"," gameId":" 5a7acf86-e22f-4cb7-912a-55b273047a4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kosihife_pukamebu_zalokiye"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947848901805","data":{"timestamp":" 947848901804"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142017"," gameId":" 5a7acf86-e22f-4cb7-912a-55b273047a4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kosihife_pukamebu_zalokiye"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947848908452","data":{"timestamp":" 947848908451"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142017"," gameId":" 5a7acf86-e22f-4cb7-912a-55b273047a4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_kirarijo_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947848915097","data":{"timestamp":" 947848915096"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142017"," gameId":" 5a7acf86-e22f-4cb7-912a-55b273047a4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_dovimahu_zazumuba"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947848921862","data":{"timestamp":" 947848921861"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142017"," gameId":" 5a7acf86-e22f-4cb7-912a-55b273047a4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_mehayehe_kirarijo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947848929386","data":{"timestamp":" 947848929386"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142017"," gameId":" 5a7acf86-e22f-4cb7-912a-55b273047a4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_mehayehe_kirarijo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947848936197","data":{"timestamp":" 947848936197"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142017"," gameId":" 5a7acf86-e22f-4cb7-912a-55b273047a4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_tujubiri_burigema_neruzugi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947848942895","data":{"timestamp":" 947848942894"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142017"," gameId":" 5a7acf86-e22f-4cb7-912a-55b273047a4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nijujuwa_fizevana_lozeyimu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947848950509","data":{"timestamp":" 947848950509"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142017"," gameId":" 5a7acf86-e22f-4cb7-912a-55b273047a4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nijujuwa_fizevana_lozeyimu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947848957158","data":{"timestamp":" 947848957158"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142017"," gameId":" 5a7acf86-e22f-4cb7-912a-55b273047a4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fopozife_jigogiki_velohuha"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947848964772","data":{"timestamp":" 947848964771"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142017"," gameId":" 5a7acf86-e22f-4cb7-912a-55b273047a4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fopozife_jigogiki_velohuha"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947848971421","data":{"timestamp":" 947848971421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142017"," gameId":" 5a7acf86-e22f-4cb7-912a-55b273047a4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_zazumuba_tetafeki_royuwika"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947848978205","data":{"timestamp":" 947848978205"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142017"," gameId":" 5a7acf86-e22f-4cb7-912a-55b273047a4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fizevana_royuwika_hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947848986114","data":{"timestamp":" 947848986113"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_142017"," gameId":" 5a7acf86-e22f-4cb7-912a-55b273047a4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_fizevana_royuwika_hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}